[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
I'm starting to wish I hadn't
shot that security guard.
His willingness to run in front of gunfire
would be real handy right about now.
I'd tell him to run out there first,
I'd run the other way,
it would be perfect.
Teamwork: the ultimate sacrifice.
Okay, time to go out in style.
Zig-zag, zig-zag--
[explosion]
[panicking, explosions]
[exhales]
Is he going to blow through the building?!
He doesn't have to!
Personally, I would recommend he
NOT blow through the building!
I shouldn't even suggest that to him.
Why is this door not moving?!
It's blown off the hinges!
I can see inside, for God's s...!
THIS IS NOT LOCKED; THIS IS CHEATING!
TELL REALITY TO STOP CHEATING!
Reality, how could you?
So, let's face the facts:
I don't have a grappling hook to
climb up the building,
and this tank needs... seconds...
to turn the barrel left and right,
so that's my window of really
shitty opportunity.
Hey, I'm not here right now.
This is my day off.
So, don't--
[explosion]
No...!
Okay, good, no second tank behind it.
Oh yeah, what now, Captain Boom-a-lot?!
How about you turn your gun towards me
and kill yourself shooting the wall?!
I'M RIGHT HERE, ASSHOLE!
COME GET ME!
THAT'S RIGHT, THIS SIDE!
Okay, bye!
Doop-boop-doop-boodloodlood-doop, doop-boop,
boo-doo-boodloodlood, doop-boop, doopboopdoop...
[missiles whistling]
[explosions]
Oh God!
Don't be a nuke! Don't be a nuke!
I-I can't handle a nuke!
Okay, I'm not blind and my face is still on
my...face, so that probably wasn't a nuke.
[gunshot]
WAAAAGH!
LOOK OUT! THERE'S A SNIPER OUTSIDE!
I SAID, LOOK OUT!
YOU NEED TO BE CAREFUL!
WATCH OUT OR HE MIGHT SHOOT YOU!
LISTEN TO ME, I SAID THERE'S A SNIPER!
I tried to warn them.
Actually, I thought that second guy was
going to run into his own grenade,
but, I think he remembered about
it at the last minute.
Some people are destined for a
special kind of greatness.
[radio rapid beeping]
Jesus Christ, this thing is loud.
I could hear it outside the building.
[radio rapid beeping]
I'm going to turn it off.
Dammit, it's not...
[radio rapid beeping]
I hit the switch, what else am I supposed to do?
I wouldn't make a good surgeon.
Hey, I just realized, I don't know
how to fly a helicopter either.
But, I think I should get a free pass on that one
because it's unreasonable to anticipate...
Okay, I'm going to let you live
because I need you for an experiment
to ascertain whether tank shells
prefer blue or orange colors.
GUARD: Sir.
Yes, that's good, you may call me "sir".
GUARD: Okay, why not? Didn't
want to die alone anyway.
Excellent.
Okay chuckles, you wait there
while I figure out where we're going.
Okay, is this...?
[lock buzzes]
No.
[distant hivehand fire]
Oh, you want to take a shot, huh?
Hey, speaking of initiative,
I can't help but notice you were standing up
here while I was screaming for help downstairs.
Some people might look poorly upon that.
Oh wow, grenades. I could've
used these a few minutes ago.
Guns!
Shells!
...more guns!
Holy crap, I've gotta find Eddie.
If I can haul all of this stuff out of here
later, this is my ticket to a new life.
Okay, I guess I can get this guard to
help me carry some of this stuff,
but we should probably find a
way out of here first
so we can come back here with a truck.
GUARD: Yep, all that target
range time is gonna pay off today.
Seriously, this might be a war zone,
but there is money to be made here!
I don't know how many MP5s I've
seen just lying on the ground.
We might need a couple trucks.
That guard knew the code to this place,
maybe he knows other stashes just like this.
He might just tell us;
what does he have to lose?
GUARD: I don't know if we should go
any further. Th-this doesn't look right.
Eddie could interrogate him later if
he doesn't, but one step at a time here.
I'll just take what I can handle for now.
I'll be using some of this just
to get out of this madhouse.
I don't have time to look
through all these crates now.
If it's anything like these
shells, we're going to cash out.
GUARD: Our luck has to change
sooner or later.
It already has!
Don't you understand that?
Forget it, all I need from you
are the stash locations, okay?
I'm not looking to split this share between
anyone else besides Eddie anyway.
I wonder if Eddie can even
handle this much inventory.
Fuck it, I know he'll try.
I know Eddie. When I tell him about all I
found that's just lying here for the taking,
he's going to get that sparkle in his eye.
It's that same sparkle he had
before he going to Panama,
and I remember how that turned out.
Oh-ho-ho! I have not forgotten you.
I mean WE haven't.
I'm not really the sentimental type, but--
Well, no, I'm not.
Okay, this must be the Sniper residence.
I received a bullet delivery from you
by mistake, so I'm returning it
plus a little something extra
for your trouble.
Okay, I'll mark down that you
received the shipment.
Hey, you don't have a car, do you?
That would make my life a lot
easier, you have no idea.
But, you probably don't;
it got blown up...?
GUARD: This place is a lot
bigger than I thought.
Oh, so you don't know
where you parked it, huh?
Well, I can't blame you.
If I knew where I was going, a few
hundred people would be alive right now.
But, they were all assholes, so...
[lock jiggles]
Yeah...
So, what kind of car do you drive?
I've been wanting to get a Crown Victoria
from a police auction for some time now.
I thought it would be cool to drive it
around town with the police stripes,
and splash some fake blood all over the hood.
[metal grinding]
Now, what is with these doors?
WHOA!
Don't turn into one of THOSE people, man.
Okay, guess we're going here.
Rrr...
GUARD: I smell an ambush.
We'd better be careful.
Hey, I'm the leader. I need you
to go find a camcorder.
Then you can film me jumping around
here and climbing on things.
If we're lucky, we'll catch some explosions
or jets flying in the background.
Then I'll mix some music to it
later; it'll look sweet.
Hey, you coming or what?
If he thinks I'm waiting on him,
he's in for a surprise.
So, this must be where that bomb hit.
Why did they bomb this? It looks empty.
Did they miss?
Maybe they don't need a reason.
Ohhh...
They'll never think to look up!
Yeah, try and advance on me from
down there, surface-dwellers!
Today's forecast is sunny mixed
with raining bullets.
Huh, so was this building bombed
before or after there were troops inside it?
Nee!
I think it was after.
Okay, how am I getting down?
Uhhh...
Oop-bop-paa!
I've lost track of how many friendly-fire
incidents I've seen the military commit by now,
but a friendly-bombing
is a new one on me.
And those are just the ones I've seen.
So, that means that the actual number
of friendly-fire incidents is a lot higher.
Anyone here?
No?
So, what happened with that bomber pilot?
Did he just sneak a flask of whiskey
up in the cockpit and take off?
Maybe he decided to do a barrel
roll when he released the bombs
so they would fan out everywhere.
And why shouldn't he if he's drunk?
JESUS CHRIST!
I almost shot you!
And how'd that door open?
Forget it; don't spook me like that!
You're really making me think about bringing
back the Kill Everyone policy I had going on.
Waah!
[exhales]
Okay...
I think I know what we're going to do here.
I mean, I think I know
what I'm going to do here.
You just...
GUARD: I'll be happy to survive
this with all my parts.
Yeah, you do that.
On a lighter note: I never told
you the second part of my plan.
The cop car is just a beginning.
The next part would take a while
because I would have to pay somebody
to train a chimpanzee in hardcore karate
and attack people on sight.
I mean, he would have to be loyal
to me, of course--I'm the trainer--
but everyone else would get a beat down.
Then we could ride around at night
and I could just let him loose
on the street for a while
watching him beat the crap out of people.
Nobody would be prepared for this.
I could have a little whistle or
something I could blow
[rumbling sound]
to get him to come back to the car.
HELLO, THIS IS GROUND CONTROL.
PLEASE APPROACH MY SIGNAL.
DO YOU SEE MY SIGNAL?
LET ME TRY ANOTHER ONE.
HOW ABOUT NOW? DO YOU SEE THAT ONE?
HELLO?
NO, NO. PLEASE STAY INSIDE THE AIRCRAFT
UNTIL AFTER YOU'VE LANDED. THANK YOU.
HOLD ON, WE'RE HAVING SOME TECHNICAL
DIFFICULTY. I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
EXCUSE ME, SIRS? SIRS? YOU'RE
NOT ALLOWED BACK HERE.
THANK YOU.
OKAY, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
CHECK THESE THROUGH CUSTOMS.
THIS IS GROUND CONTROL AGAIN.
YOU'RE FLYING SOUTH.
FOLLOW MY SIGNAL.
IF YOU DECIDE YOU WANT TO KEEP ON FLYING
TO ANOTHER AIRFIELD, THAT'S FINE BY ME.
JUST KEEP GOING...somewhere.
[metal grinding]
WE'RE GOING TO NEED MAINTENANCE DOWN HERE.
WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM WITH THE HANGAR DOORS.
OKAY, YOU'RE HEADING BACK EAST?
AH, YOU'RE COMING AROUND.
OKAY, LET'S LINE IT UP THEN.
YOUR APPROACH LOOKS GOOD
I'M JUST GOING TO GUIDE YOU IN.
JUST FOLLOW MY SIGNAL.
LOOKING GOOD!
PERFECT!
Welcome to New Mexico. Ground temperatures
are 88 degrees with clear skies.
Thank you for flying with us.
Those aircraft didn't have the
best safety records anyway.
I don't need to be checked by
Security; I work here? Thank you.
[lock buzzes]
Well, I don't want to go in
there anyway!
Yep, have shotgun, will travel.
One thing I don't--
WAAH!
Shit!
Not again!
Okay, walk away.
I'm not getting involved
anymore than I am already.
It's not like I can get
into any more trouble.
What do I care? I launched a missile.
Besides, I FUCKING TOLD HIM NOT TO DO THAT!
So, what does he do? He does it again.
That's the story of humanity right there.
He didn't even find a camcorder.